{
    "subject": "resource/Hawking_(2013_film)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Hawking",
    "human_readable": "The name of the film 'Hawking' (2013) is Hawking.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9647366404533386,
            "question": "What is the name of the film released in 2013 about Stephen Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8338396549224854,
            "question": "Is the title of the film 'Hawking' the same as the subject of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7380473613739014,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film 'Hawking'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322691679000854,
            "question": "Who is the likely focus of the film titled 'Hawking'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548219919204712,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'Hawking' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761252045631409,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who might have played Stephen Hawking in the film 'Hawking'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5045884251594543,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Hawking' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5045329928398132,
            "question": "What are some potential themes explored in the film 'Hawking'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3650258481502533,
            "question": "What kind of impact do you think a film about Stephen Hawking could have on viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3290761113166809,
            "question": "Would you be interested in watching the film 'Hawking'? Why or why not?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the film 'Hawking' (2013) is Hawking.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3539_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of impact do you think a film about Stephen Hawking could have on viewers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3539_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential themes explored in the film 'Hawking'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3539_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Hawking' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3539_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3539_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports that there was a film titled \"Hawking\" released in 2013, as mentioned in multiple documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}